meeting of the Miami-Skush utility authority. I am through this innovation by the
retired pastor of first-person church, Leon Wiesley. I'd like to be in here tonight.
Oh, there I thank you for the people in this room. People who are out there also all through
the week. Right here in the room, Father, you blessed them, blessed me with wisdom, energy,
a great critique here of them. And then these ones up here behind the desk.
Thank you for your job as often thankers. Lord, you've given them intelligence.
And I pray that they will rely heavily on that. And Lord, I also ask that you will let them
sense you calling to them and talk to them. Thank you for our help. And that created you bless this new
night. Jesus name, I pray. And then Doug, would you please lead the pledge? Sure. I pledge allegiance to the
flag of the United States of America, thanks to the Republic for which it stands. One nation under God
in it is with liberty and justice for our help. Thank you, Lord. I have them for his public income and
substantial personal appearances and he wanted us to address the utility authority on any of the
agenda items. Item five is consent agenda staff is recommending item six to eight, which are
clean claims, minutes and budget amendments for the consent agenda. There are no questions on you,
those items and they're trying to motion to approve that is recommended. Second place, second
event. Or call? Or kid? Lewis. Aye. What's them? Aye. Shulps. Aye. Item nine is
except of reject bid C1937 and the amount of a million 1,1,2,700 to capital electric line builders for a
13,1 to the killable substation for expansion to substation one. And approved the contract contingent
on submission required contract documents, approved city manager, ordered gues of me as I know this to proceed.
I think this is the actual construction. So we came up with you, you know, to buy different pieces of
a substation now, we're going to put it all together. So now we're, if you remember, we rejected the previous
bid, because they came in a lot higher than estimated, we re-bid, and we actually came in and saw the
below our engineers estimate on both of them. So I'm here happy about that. Okay. Any questions? I'm
like I'm always too approved. We have a second. Second. roll call please. So aye.
Question. Aye. Lewis. Aye. Or kid? Aye. And then item 10 is bid C1938A for a million 856 for the
similar same project that substation. So this has been wanted by nickel substation. Thank you for
this one. And if we get a better deal, because they're combining the two together or this bit.
in their schedule, this is a good winter project for them while they're waiting on the
spring start up.
And this one also came in below estimates, also.
Mike and most to the 110 to accept the C1938 A, do we have a second?
I'll second it.
Roll pro please.
So, I.
Loomis, aye.
What's there?
Aye.
I was 11 as a new business, any of you business anyone?
We're always trustee community announcements, any announcements?
13 is adjournment.
We have most to adjourn the issue I mean.
We're adjourned.
Second up please.
Second pro call.
Weston.
Aye.